[
    {
        "question": "How many oceans border Canada?",
        "answer": "Three",
        "others": ["One", "Four", "None"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Canada's National sport?",
        "answer": "Hockey",
        "others": ["Curling", "Skiing", "Volleyball"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Capital of Canada?",
        "answer": "Ottawa",
        "others": ["Vancouver", "St. John's", "Toronto"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is in the center of the canadian flag?",
        "answer": "Maple Leaf",
        "others": ["Beaver", "Moose", "Birch Lead"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which province of Canada has a predominantly French population?",
        "answer": "Quebec",
        "others": ["British Columbia", "Ontario", "Nova Scotia"]
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False; Canada is the world's second largest country, by land mass?",
        "answer": "True",
        "others": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the most recent territory to join Canada?",
        "answer": "Nunavut",
        "others": ["Northwest Territories", "Labrador", "Yukon"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Canadian $1 coin called?",
        "answer": "Loonie",
        "others": ["Beaver Tail", "Moose Dropping", "Canuck"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many timezones cover the country?",
        "answer": "6",
        "others": ["2", "12", "1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did Canada become a country?",
        "answer": "1867",
        "others": ["1786", "1682", "1912"]
    },
]
